我们要永远关上地狱之门
We're about to close the gates of hell forever.
迪恩・温彻斯特
(英勇的猎人)
走过的路
你一直在炼狱
You were in Purgatory?
让我觉得纯粹
It felt pure.
我不做猎人了  我找到了一些东西
I don't hunt anymore. I found something.
你找我了吗
Did you look for me?
凯文・谭
Kevin Tran.
以为你能躲我一辈子吗
Thought you could elude me forever?
上帝建立了一系列测试
God built a series of tests.
等你都完成了  就可以去关地狱之门了
When you've done all three, you can slam the gates of hell.
-第一项是什么  -杀一只地狱之犬
- Where do we start? - Kill a hound of hell.
从地狱拯救一个无辜的灵魂
An innocent soul has to be rescued from hell
并将它送入天堂
and delivered unto heaven.
最后的测试
And the final test?
治愈一个恶魔
To cure a demon.
阿比顿  她是一个地狱骑士
Abbadon, a knight of hell.
她跑了
She's gone.
我叫娜奥米
My name is Naomi.
我们救了你
We rescued you.
天使石碑
The angel tablet.
我不会伤害迪恩
I won't hurt Dean.
杀了他
Kill him.
我们是一家人
We're family.
我要保护这块石碑
I have to protect this tablet now.
这些测试
These trials --
它们在净化我
...they're purifying me.
-梅塔特隆  -我是神的书记员
- Metatron? - I'm the scribe of god.
天堂需要你的帮助  卡西迪奥
Heaven needs your help, Castiel.
我在杀你们救过的每一个人
I'm killing everyone you've ever saved.
也许我们就该接受条件
Maybe we should just take the deal.
测试  全部都放弃
The trials -- you'll give them up.
我们会像以往一样打个漂亮仗
Kick it in the ass like we always do.
你要和我一起吗
Are you with me?
如今
免费的  警长
On the house, sheriff.
谢谢  南茜  但我没点
Oh, thanks, Nance, but I didn't order --
-那么...  -祝你好运
- So... - Good luck.
我们要喝什么
...what are we drinking?
罗德里克
Roderick?
乔迪啊
Wow, Jody.
我简直无法形容
Words cannot begin to describe
那张照片是多么有辱你的美貌
the injustice that that picture does to you.
少来了
Come on.
-怎么  -瞧瞧你啊
- What? - Look at you.
好工作  好西服
The fancy career, the suit.
而我不过就是个小镇女人
I'm pretty much what I am -- small-town girl.
但我们是有共同点的
We do share something, you and I.
什么
What?
失去亲人
Loss.
我的儿子和丈夫
My son and my husband.
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
我也失去过亲人
I've lost someone, too.
非要流眼泪才叫约会呢
It's not a date till I've cried.
现在你流过泪了
So now you've cried.
这真是疯了
Oh, this is crazy.
真是疯了
This is crazy.
我疯了
I'm crazy.
不过他是挺有魅力的
He's attractive, though, right?
挺性感的
He's hot.
[咒语]
Manu mortis accesso,
spiritus vitae recedit.
给你们一分钟  然后你们一位亲切可爱
You have less than one minute before a very dear, attractive,
略有醉意的朋友就会断气
and slightly tipsy friend of yours snuffs it.
停手吧  克劳力
Call it off, Crowley.
为什么
Because?
因为都结束了  你个混蛋
Because it's over, you son of a bitch.
我们愿意交易
We want to deal.
三十秒
30 seconds.
我们停止测试  你停止杀戮
We stop the trials, and you stop the killing.
我要恶魔石碑  整块石碑
I want the demon tablet -- the whole demon tablet.
好吧  但天使石碑得给我们
Fine, but then the angel tablet comes to us.
凭什么
On what grounds?
因为你是个混蛋
On the grounds that you're a douche bag
混蛋不能掌握那么大的力量
and no douche bag should have that much power.
交不交易
Deal or not?
首先  对我说一句话
First, I need to hear two little words --
我投降
I surrender.
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第二十三集
牺牲
你把恶魔石碑藏在了魔鬼下面
You hid the demon tablet underneath the devil?
不是吧
Seriously?
怎么了  我当时神志不清
What? I was delirious.
你确定这样能行吗
You sure this is gonna work?
我们还有别的办法吗
What choice do we have?
好吧  听着  这是一个秘密藏身处
All right, listen, this is a secret lair.
明白吗
You understand me?
别带酒友去
No keggers.
我没有朋友
I don't have any friends.
低调点就是了
Yeah, well, just lay low.
谁知道呢
Who knows?
说不定你马上就能回去参加奥数了
You'll be a mathlete again before you know it.
伙计们
You guys?
你们这么做是对的
You're doing the right thing.
上帝保佑你  欢迎捐助
德克萨斯州  休斯顿
他什么样
What was he like?
谁
Who?
上帝吗
Oh. God?
就跟你想的一样
Mm, pretty much like you'd expect.
神圣伟岸  暴脾气
Larger-than-life, gruff,
有点性别歧视
bit of a sexist.
但十分公正
But fair -- eminently fair.
那个拿非利人不是好东西  卡西迪奥
The nephilim was a monster, Castiel.
下一项测试呢
And the next trial?
就在街对面
Across the street.
他叫德怀特・查尔斯
His name is Dwight Charles.
我一直在天使无线电上听
I've been listening in on the angel radio.
准确说是丘比特频道
Cupid frequency, actually.
他就是他们下一个目标
And he is the next on their list.
目标
Their list?
跳水平曼波舞
To do the horizontal mambo.
碰碰肚皮[两句都暗指性交]
Slap bellies.
找到爱情
To find love.
懂了
Oh. Yes.
就是他
Well, that.
他在24小时之内就要被丘比特之箭射中
He's slotted to be dinged by cupid's arrow within 24 hours,
这对我们正好  因为第二项测试
which is good for us, because the second trial
就是拿到一把丘比特的弓
is retrieving cupid's bow.
不用杀人吗
No killing?
不用
No killing.
南达柯达州  苏福尔斯
你们好啊
Hello, boys.
怎么说的来着
What's that old expression?
成功有很多父亲
Success has many fathers.
原话是成功有很多父亲  失败是个孤儿
失败姓温彻斯特
Failure is a Winchester.
石头在哪
Where's the stone?
你把你的拿出来  我们才会拿出来
You show us yours, and we'll show you ours.
不是吧  迪恩
Really, Dean?
我在尽力进行专业的谈判
I'm trying to conduct a professional negotiation here,
你却说起老二来了
and you want to talk dangly bits?
石碑
The stone.
慢慢的
Slowly.
在那儿呢
There she is.
合同呢
And the contract?
这里面肯定没有问题
Yeah, I'm sure there's no hidden agendas in there.
关键部分  我们交换石碑
The highlights -- we swap tablets,
你们永远放弃测试
you stand down from the trials forever.
你停止杀害我们救过的人
You stop killing everyone we've ever saved.
同意
Agreed.
想得美  小松鼠
Nice try, squirrel.
小鹿在做测试
Moose is doing these trials.
小鹿来签字
Moose signs.
不行
No, no, no.
我没把合同一字不落地看完  他不能签
He's not signing anything until I read the fine print.
我自己会看
I can read it.
你要我来  所以我来了
Hey, you wanted me here. I'm here.
但我绝不会允许他进一步坑我们
But I'll be damned if I'm gonna let him screw us even more.
这是干什么
What's this?
天堂也有烦恼了吗
Trouble in paradise, boys?
怎么了  纳撒尼尔
What is it, Nathaniel?
有一个自由外派员来找我们了
One of our freelancers has reached out to us.
他找到了卡西迪奥
He's found Castiel.
他在哪
Where?
德克萨斯休斯顿一家酒吧里
A drinking establishment in Houston, Texas.
而且
And...
怎么了
What?
他说卡西迪奥不是一个人
He says Castiel was not alone.
他跟谁在一起
Who was he with?
从描述来看  我觉得是他
By the description, I-I think it was him --
书记员
The scribe.
你要一直这么默念  是吧
You're gonna move your lips the whole way up here, aren't you?
你知道我为什么总赢吗
You know why I always defeat you?
是因为你们的人性
It's your humanity.
是内置的缺陷
It's a built-in handicap.
你们总把情感放在常识之前
You always put emotion ahead of good, old-fashioned common sense.
我们让那个大傻瓜签了吧
Let's have the big galoot sign it now, shall we?
这是开玩笑吗
Is this a joke?
你知道我只要
You realize all I have to do is...
恶魔手铐  混蛋
Demonic handcuffs, jackass.
弹指响  瞬间传送  黑烟出窍都不好使
No flicking, no teleporting, no smoking out --
还有  交易也没门
Oh, and... no deal.
所以你得听我们的了
Which pretty much means that you're our bitch.
好啊
Fine.
你想跟我玩手铐  好啊
You want to play chain gang? Let's.
我可不是好惹的
You saddled yourself to the wrong bull, mate.
我可以这么玩一整天  你知道吗
I can do this all day, 'cause you know what?
这感觉棒极了
Damn, it feels good!
但不管如何
But sooner or later,
你早晚得承认  你归我们了
you're gonna have to face it -- you're ours.
所以你这个恶魔
Which means that your demon ass
很快就要变成一个常人了
is going to be a mortal ass pretty damn quick.
他在说什么呢
What's he mouthing on about?
你就是第三道测试  克劳力
You're the third trial, Crowley.
你在看什么啊
What're you reading?
择偶启示
Personal advertisements.
那男人尽早找到爱情  丘比特也能尽早来
The faster that man finds love, the faster the cupid will come.
相信我
Trust me.
我朋友的朋友就是干这个的
I'm friends with friends who do this for a living.
-来点什么吗  -嗯
- Help you gents? - Yes.
你是想找一个
Would you say that you're looking for, uh,
犯罪伙伴
a partner in crime...
还是
...or, uh,
略有支配欲  喜欢扮演护士的女人呢
someone who's into nurse role-play and light domination?
伙计  现在是周二早上十点啊
Brother, it's 10:00 a.m. on a Tuesday.
我们要两杯啤酒
Uh, we'll have two drafts, please.
这就来
Coming up.
你还真是不知委婉是何物啊
You're not the most subtle tool in the shed, are you?
杀了他
Kill him.
下一枪不会打偏了
Next one won't wing you.
滚去别地方打
Take it someplace else.
放了他
Let him go.
你制造的麻烦还不够多吗  卡西迪奥
Haven't you caused enough harm already, Castiel?
住手  求你  卡西迪奥  别弄得更糟了
Stop. Please, Castiel, don't make this any worse.
求你
Please.
你真觉得这东西能束缚得了我
You really think this is gonna hold me,
你们能治愈我还是什么的
that you're gonna cure me or whatever it is?
他可以了
He's primed.
感觉如何
How you feeling?
说实话  很久以来  我第一次
Honestly, for the first time in a long time,
觉得我们能赢
it feels like we're gonna win.
我很好
I'm good.
好吧  没完事之前先别高兴得太早
All right, well, no dancing in the end zone until we're finished.
神父的指导书里怎么说的
What's the good father's playbook say now?
嗯
Well...
我们有圣地了
Now that we got the consecrated ground,
我只要
I just, uh
每小时给克劳力注射一剂血  持续八小时
I slip Crowley one dose of blood every hour for eight hours
再用血手三明治完成仪式
and seal the deal with a bloody-fist sandwich.
应该就行了
That should do it.
你的血得净化过  对吧
Your blood's supposed to be purified, isn't it?
你以前做过忏悔吗
You ever, uh -- you ever done the "forgive me, father" before?
做过一次  小时候做的
Well, once, when we were kids.
所以我现在完全不知道该说什么
Which is why I have no clue what to say now.
如果需要的话  我可以提议一些
Well, I mean, I could give you suggestions if you want.
好啊  说吧
O-okay. Yeah, sure.
好
All right.
我就想到什么说什么
Well, I'm just spit-balling here,
但如果我是你
but if I were you, uh...
就说露比  杀莉莉丝
Ruby, killing Lilith,
把路西法放出来  失去你的灵魂
letting Lucifer out, losing your soul,
我去炼狱之后没来找我
not looking for me when I went to purgatory,
-谢谢  -也就开个头
- Thanks. - for starters.
还有你六年级的时候
Or, hey, h-how about what you did to, uh,
对佩妮・马克尔做的事呢
Penny Markle in the sixth grade?
先说那件吧
Why don't you lead with that?
那是你干的
Well, that was you.
你快去吧
Carry on.
好吧
Okay, um...
如果有人在听  我开始了
...if anybody's listening, here goes.
迪恩  我需要你帮忙
Dean, I need your help.
略忙  小卡  排号吧
Little busy, Cass. Take a number.
恐怕这事刻不容缓
I'm afraid this can't wait.
娜奥米带走了梅塔特隆
Naomi has taken Metatron.
你怎么认识梅塔特隆的
And you know Metatron how?
我在跟他一起进行天使测试
I've been working with him on the angel trials.
什么  我们要关闭一切
The what? We're gonna shut it all down --
天堂  地狱  都关上
Heaven, hell, all of it.
我听说过你
I know you.
我们还没正式见过
We've never officially met.
娜奥米
Naomi.
你名声远扬啊
Your reputation precedes you.
那些大天使
The archangels --
上帝走后他们让我向你打听情况
Wanted me to debrief you after God left.
打听情况
"Debrief" me.
真是这样吗
Is that what you call it?
你无从得知了  不是吗
Well, how would you know?
我还没来得及找你  你就跑了
You ran before I had the chance.
但  我们还是走到了这一步
But...here we are.
但是我们开始之前我还有一个问题
I just have one question before we begin.
你肯定知道我们会竭力抓住
You had to know that we would leap at the chance
从你脑子里挖取上帝的秘密的机会
to extract all of God's secrets from that head of yours,
所以我不禁自问  为什么
Which is why I ask myself...why?
为什么书记员突然冒了出来
Why did the scribe suddenly come in from the shadows?
而且你跟卡西迪奥在一起干什么
And what are you doing with Castiel?
当恩赐摆在面前
"Of the blessings set before you,
塞缪尔・约翰逊  英作家  批评家
做出选择  并知足常乐
make your choice and be content."
不怎么读书  是吧
Not a big reader, are we?
梅塔特隆  那个疯疯癫癫
Metatron, the guy who was full-on crazy,
囤积狂的老天使
cat-lady-hoarder angel yesterday --
现在想拯救天堂
now he wants to save heaven?
是的
Yes, he wants to.
但只有我能做到
But I'm the only one who can.
我不能失败  迪恩
I can't fail, Dean,
这次不行  我需要你帮忙
not on this one. I need your help.
听我说  小卡  这很好
Look, Cass, that's all well and good, okay,
但你是让我离开萨姆
But you're asking me to leave Sam,
而且克劳力就被绑在里面呢
and we've got Crowley in there tied and tressed.
如果说有谁完成艰巨任务
Now, if anybody needs a chaperone
需要有人陪着就是萨姆了
while doing the heavy lifting, it's Sam.
你去吧
You should go.
真的
Seriously.
然后扔下你一人对付地狱之王吗
Oh, what, and leave you here with the king of hell?
得了吧
Come on.
我行的
I got this.
如果你们还能把天使都关起来
And if you guys can lock the angels up, too...
那就太好了
That's a good day.
听我说
Look, I...
我也愿意把天使送回天堂去
I'm down with sending the angels back to heaven,
因为他们太混蛋了
just 'cause they're dicks.
但恶魔
But the demons?
这是我们的事
This is on us.
现在就开始注射
Start the injections now.
要是我八小时后还没回来  了结这事
If I'm not back in eight hours, finish it,
别质疑  别犹豫
no questions, no hesitation.
你真觉得给我注射人类的血
You really think injecting me with human blood
就能把我转化成人吗
is gonna make me human?
这是在麦片盒上看到的吗
Did you read that on the back of a cereal box?
你太自不量力了  小鹿
You're miles out of your league, moose.
一小时后见
See you in an hour.
这是在开玩笑吗
Is this a joke?
不  是神之语
No. It's the word of God.
-什么  -这是块石碑
- What? - It's a tablet.
翻译一下  你就是干这个的
All right, translate. That's what you do.
这是天使之碑
Okay. Um, it's the angel tablet,
我这辈子从没见过
which I've never laid eyes on in my life.
我翻译半块恶魔石碑
You want a translation in like six hours
花了六个月  妈妈还死了
when it took me six months and a dead mom
现在你要我六小时译出天使石碑
to translate a piece of the demon tablet?
用你早上的话来说
And according to your own words this morning...
我现在不干了
this is not what I do.
这是我过去干的事
It's what I did.
是你说我可以抽身了  迪恩
You told me I was out, Dean.
-是的...  -你要是准备说
- Yeah, well -- - And if this is gonna be
"我们这种人永远无法抽身"  省省吧
the "guys like us are never out" speech, save it.
-迪恩说得对  -小卡
- Dean's right. - Cass!
无法抽身  只有责任
There is no out. Only duty.
放开我
Get the hell off me.
你是上帝的先知  永远都是
You are a prophet of the lord, always and forever...
直到你死去
until the day you cease to exist,
另一位先知接替你的职位
and then another prophet takes your place.
你清楚自己眼前的任务了吗
Now, are you clear as to the task before you?
那就做吧  我们走
Then do it, and let's go.
搞什么  克劳力
What the hell, Crowley?
咬人  不是吧
Biting?! Seriously?!
[咒语]
Inferni sectatores, nunc audite regem.
看在一切的分上  要是有人听到
For the love of everything, whoever is hearing this --
不管是谁  我是你的王
If anyone is hearing this -- this is your king.
马上找人来帮忙
Send help immediately.
找到什么了吗  你去了很久
Anything? You've been gone long enough.
没有
No.
有一个女性  但是...
There was one female, but...
怎么了
What?
我觉得"她"好像不是女性
I don't think she was female.
这里有什么吗
Anything here?
免费酒水
Free drinks.
你那个兄弟觉得你救了他一命
Your, uh, buddy over there thinks you saved his life.
你觉得工作时喝酒明智吗
Do you really think it's wise to be drinking on the job?
你都白跟我混了啊
What show you been watching?
告诉我
Talk to me.
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
我和萨姆关地狱之门是一回事
I mean, it's one thing me and Sammy slamming the gates to the pit,
但你要封掉天堂
but you -- you're -- you're boarding up heaven,
把自己也关进去
and you're locking the door behind you.
我知道
Yeah. I know.
你在那上面造成的伤害可不小  伙计
You did a lot of damage up there, man.
你觉得他们会放过你吗
You think they're just gonna let that slide?
你是想问  我是否认为他们会杀我
Do you mean do I think they'll kill me?
也许吧
Yeah, they might.
就这样了吗
So this is it?
ET回家了
E.T. goes home.
你好啊
Hey, there.
艾德在哪
Where's Ed?
-得流感了  我叫盖尔  -好吧
- Flu. I'm Gail. - Well, okay, then.
好戏上演
Showtime.
让我帮你吧
Let me give you a hand.
谢了
Oh, thanks.
你真是个绅士
You're a real gentleman.
天哪  这简直就是我看过的所有毛片
Holy crud, this is like the first five minutes
前五分钟的戏码
of every porno I've ever seen.
谢了
Thanks.
这位是盖尔  这位是罗德
Gail, Rod.
-女士  -罗德是这儿的常客
- Ma'am. - Rod rides a stool here most days.
二位回见
I'll be seeing you both.
谢谢帮忙
Thanks for the help.
不客气
No problem.
妈的  太帅了
Damn, that's sweet.
下一杯我请吧
How about the next one's on me?
怎么样了  小鹿
How we doing, moose?
不是到了爱心注射的时候了吗
Ain't it about time for the next love injection?
改...改...改变
Ch-ch-ch-ch-changes,
转身面对那奇怪的
turn and face the strange
改...改...改变
ch-ch-changes.
必须要重新做人
Just gonna have to be a different man.
时光或许改变了我  但我无法追踪...
Time may change me, but I can't trace --
你真以为能够绑架地狱之王
Did you really think you could kidnap the king of hell
而不被人察觉吗  傻蛋
and no one was gonna notice, dumb nuts?!
你们好啊
Hello, boys.
那是我的台词
That's my line.
阿比顿
Abbadon?
他们说你死了
They told me you were dead.
活蹦乱跳呢
So not.
剩下的人呢
And the rest of the cavalry?
没了  只有我这个老不死的
Oh, no, it's just little, old, unkillable me.
真棒
Brilliant.
有骑士还要步兵做什么
Why send in a few grunts when you can send in a knight?
祈祷吧  小鹿
Say your prayers, moose.
这也行
That'll do.
帮我松绑
Undo these.
我要亲自干掉他
I'll kill him myself.
那是命令吗
That was an order, was it?
我是你的王
I am your king.
这个嘛
About that...
你好  兄弟
Hello, brother.
把你的弓给我
Give us your bow.
什么
What?
先礼后兵
Talk first, stab later.
你知道我从一个衣柜穿越到了2013年
Do you know what I find the most shocking about time-traveling
最让我震惊的是什么吗
through a closet and landing in the year 2013?
居然有人会让你来当地狱之王
Somebody thought it was a good idea to make you the king of hell.
你知道那小屁孩想干什么吧
You know what that boy's trying to do, right?
他想关闭地狱之门
He's trying to shut the gates of hell.
我们现在得先谈谈改朝换代的事
Right now you and I are gonna talk about regime change.
臭婊子
You little whore.
我是你的王...
I am your k--
肉身不错
I love the suit.
我已经很久不敢回家了
I've been afraid to go home for some time now.
以前每天都有命令  如今却是一片混乱
Orders used to come once a day, and now it's chaos.
一切似乎都崩溃了
It all seems to be breaking down.
你觉得你能修复这一切
And you think you can fix that?
只是需要一点时间
With time, yes.
那就拿去吧
Take it, then.
你在我脑子里好顿折腾啊
You've been digging.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this -- this?
你知道我这种籍籍无名之徒
Do you have any idea what it would be like
被上帝擢升
to be plucked from obscurity,
坐在他脚下
to sit at God's feet,
让我记录他的话语是什么感觉吗
to be asked to write down his word?
他走后我心痛不已
The ache I felt when he was gone,
我不断告诉自己  "父亲走了"
telling myself, "Father's left,
但看看他留给了我们什么  天堂
but look what he's left us -- paradise.
但你和那些大天使
But you and your archangels
却不安于现状
couldn't leave well enough alone.
你们逼得我远离家园
You ran me from my home.
你以为你们对我做出那等恶行
Did you really think you could do all of that to me
还能全身而退吗
and there'd be no payback?
刚刚表现得很好啊  小鹿
You did good back there, moose.
我当然不会承认说过这话  但我很骄傲
I'll deny it if you ever quote me, but I'm a proud man.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
谢了
Thanks.
等等  那是什么
Hold on. Uh, w-what's that?
你自己看呢
It's what it looks like.
你开玩笑吧
Are you joking?
我刚刚救了你
I just saved your life.
-别搞笑了  -搞笑  我搞笑
- Seriously? - Seriously? Me, seriously?
我们刚刚可是并肩作战啊
We just shared a foxhole, you and I.
我们挫败了春节攻势[越战战役]
We beat back the Tet Offensive,
一起躲过了南京大屠杀
outrun the -- the Rape of Nanking together!
你居然还要这样对我
And still you're gonna do me like this?!
《兄弟连》  《太平洋战争》
"Band of brothers"? "The pacific"?
你完全没看过吗
None of this means anything to you?
你待过那么多旅馆
All those motels,
居然一次都没看过HBO台
you never once watched HBO, not once?
《衰姐们》
"Girls"?
你就是我的玛妮啊  小鹿
You're my Marnie, moose.
还有汉娜  她只是想有人爱她
A-and Hannah -- she just -- she needs to be loved.
那是她应得的
She deserves it.
我们每个人  你  我  都该得到爱啊
Don't we all -- you, me -- we deserve to be loved.
我该得到爱
I deserve to be loved!
我只是得到爱
I just want to be loved.
你说什么
What?
什么
如果可以的话  小鹿
Would it be possible, moose...
你能否答应我一个请求  萨姆
I'd like... to ask you a-a favor, Sam.
刚才
Earlier,
你在里面忏悔的时候
when you were confessing back there...
都说了什么
...what did you say?
我这么问是因为
I only ask because,
鉴于我的过去
given my history...
我得好好考虑
...it raises the question...
我要从哪开始
Where do I start...
寻求宽恕
...to even look for forgiveness?
我是说
I mean...
就从这一针开始吧
How about we start with this?
我想我找到了天使测试
I think I found the angel trials,
但我找不到任何关于拿非利人
but I don't see anything about a Nephilim
或丘比特之弓之类的东西
or a Cupid's bow or anything like that.
不能吧  凯文
Oh, come on, Kev!
我们离终点线就只差一步了
We're on the one-yard line here.
好吧  我六个月前就该提出这个的
Okay, a-and I should have mentioned this six months ago,
别用体育隐喻来激励我
but the sports metaphors -- y-you want to motivate me,
魔术卡片  天际  阿兹・安萨里
"Magic Cards, "Skyrim," Aziz Ansari.
你说什么
What?
我根本不知道你在说什么
Yeah, I don't know what those words mean.
我不是来和你打架的  卡西迪奥
I'm not here to fight you, Castiel.
迪恩
Dean?
再也不会了
Not anymore.
迪恩
Dean?
梅塔特隆在哪
Where is Metatron?
他告诉你他要挽救天堂  对不对
He told you he was going to fix heaven, didn't he?
杀掉一个拿非利人  切下一个丘比特之弓
Murdering a Nephilim, cutting off a Cupid's bow --
那些全是谎言
It's a lie, all of it.
我读过他的思想
I've been in his head.
你读过我们每个人的思想
You've been in all our heads.
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
不  卡西迪奥  你错了
No, Castiel, you're wrong.
你就是那样的人
This is what you do.
你扭曲事实
You twist things.
我在努力挽救天堂
I'm trying to fix heaven.
梅塔特隆也在挽救天堂
Metatron is trying to fix heaven.
梅塔特隆没打算挽救任何东西
Metatron isn't trying to fix anything.
他想要毁掉天堂
He's trying to break it.
为曾被逼走复仇
An act of revenge for driving him away.
怎么毁掉
Break it how?
迪恩
Dean.
驱逐天堂所有天使
Expel all angels from heaven,
就像上帝驱逐路西法那样
just as God cast out Lucifer.
驱逐到哪  地狱
Cast you out to where? Hell?
这里
Here.
成千上万的天使  下至人间
Thousands of us, walking the earth.
-你说谎  -等等
- Lies. - Wait!
我们的使命是保护上帝所创造的一切
Our mission was to protect what God created.
我不知道我们何时忘掉了
I don't know when we forgot that.
我非常想看到你关上地狱之门
I want nothing more than to see you shut the gates of hell,
但我曾说你可以信任我
but I told you that you could trust me.
如果萨姆完成了测试
If Sam completes those trials,
他就会死去
he is going to die.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
我在梅塔特隆的脑海里看到了
I saw it in Metatron's head.
这本来就是上帝的意图  最终的牺牲
It was always God's intention -- the ultimate sacrifice.
至于你  卡西迪奥
As for you, Castiel,
我求你  住手吧
I beg of you, stop this path.
梅塔特隆已经被制服了
Metatron has been neutralized.
如果你想回归  我会听你的
If you want back in, truly, I will listen.
马上告诉我
Hey, right now, talk to me.
她是在撒谎吗
Is she lying?
我不知道
I don't know.
快查出真相
Well, find out!
-她在说谎  -把我去他那儿
- She's lying. - Take me to him.
-迪恩  -快带我去他那儿
- Dean. - Take me to him now!
[咒语]
Exorcizamus te, omnis immundus spiritus,
Hanc animam redintegra, lustra.
迪恩  我没有错
Dean, I'm not wrong.
我要挽救我的家园
I'm going to fix my home.
小卡
Cass!
小萨姆  停下
Sammy, stop!
她告诉你我说谎了  是吧
She told you I lied, didn't she?
你真应该听那个婊子的
You should've listened to the bitch.
别激动  好吗
Easy there, Okay?
别激动  我们的计划有微小的变动
Just take it easy. We got a slight change of plan.
什么  出什么事了
What? What's going on?
-小卡在哪  -梅塔特隆说谎了
- Where's Cass?! - Metatron lied.
你完成了测试  你就会死掉  萨姆
You finish this trial, you're dead, Sam.
那又怎样
So?
你发誓过
You promised.
卡西迪奥  别再去想什么大计划
Castiel, I want you to stop thinking about master plans,
天堂  天使  和这一切
heaven and angels, and all this.
那再也跟你没关系了
That doesn't concern you anymore.
那些根本就不是测试  卡西迪奥
These were never trials, Castiel.
这是咒语
This is a spell.
我现在从你身体里抽取的
And what I'm taking from you now --
你的精髓  你的能量
Your essence, your grace --
是最后的元素
is the last piece.
无比美妙的事情即将发生
And now something wonderful is going to happen,
对你  对我  都是如此
for me and for you.
我希望你尽情享受你的新生活
I want you to live this new life to the fullest.
找个老婆
Find a wife.
生一堆小孩
Make babies.
等你死后  你的灵魂会重回天堂
And when you die and your soul comes to heaven,
来找我
find me.
告诉我你的故事
Tell me your story.
去吧
Now go.
看看他
Look at him.
看看他  成功近在咫尺
Look at him! Look how close we are!
如果我不完成  会有其他人死去
Other people will die if I don't finish this!
想想吧
Think about it.
想想我们知道什么
Think about what we know, huh?
把灵魂从地狱中拉回来  治愈恶魔
Pulling souls from hell, curing demons,
见鬼  猎杀地狱犬
hell, ganking a hellhound!
我们了解的知识足以扭转乾坤
We have enough knowledge on our side to turn the tide here.
但是没有你  我做不到
But I can't do it without you.
你和我一起也很难做到
You can barely do it with me.
你觉得我把一切都搞砸了
I mean, you think I screw up everything I try.
你觉得我需要人陪着  记得吗
You think I need a chaperone, remember?
别这样  老弟  我不是那个意思
Come on, man. That's not what I meant.
不  你就是这个意思
No, it's exactly what you meant.
你想知道我在那里忏悔了什么吗
You want to know what I confessed in there?
我最大的罪过是什么
What my greatest sin was?
就是我让你失望过太多次
It was how many times I let you down.
我再也不能这么做了
I can't do that again.
萨姆
Sam --
如果你又觉得你不能信任我怎么办
What happens when you've decided I can't be trusted again?
下一次你不信任我时会去找谁
I mean, who are you gonna turn to next time instead of me?
再找个天使  再找个
Another angel, another --
再找个吸血鬼吗
Another vampire?
你知道那是什么感觉吗
Do you have any idea what it feels like
-看着你的哥哥...  -打住
- to watch your brother just -- - Hold on, hold on!
你真的这么想吗
You seriously think that?
因为事实绝不是你说的那样
Because none of it -- none of it -- is true.
老弟  我知道我们有分歧
Listen, man, I know we've had our disagreements, okay?
我知道我说过一些混蛋话让你感到沮丧
Hell, I know I've said some junk that set you back on your heels.
但是  小萨姆  别这样
But, Sammy...come on.
我为了救你  害死了本尼
I killed Benny to save you.
为了让你活下去
I'm willing to let this bastard
我愿放过这个混蛋和其他害死妈妈的混蛋
and all the sons of bitches that killed mom walk because of you.
过去或现在  你怎么可以认为
Don't you dare think that there is anything, past or present,
我会把任何事看得比你还重
that I would put in front of you!
绝不是那样的  绝不是
It has never been like that, ever!
我需要你看清这一点
I need you to see that.
我求你
I'm begging you.
我要怎么停下
How do I stop?
放弃吧
Jus let it go.
做不到  迪恩  这在我体内
I can't. It's in me, dean.
你不知道这是什么感觉
You don't know what this feels like.
我们会想到办法的  好吗
Hey, listen, we will figure it out, okay,
一如往常
just like we always do.
来吧
Come on.
来  放弃吧  好吗
Come on. Let it go, okay?
放弃吧  老弟
Let it go, brother.
迪恩
Hey, Dean.
看
See?
萨姆
Sam?
我在  弟弟  你会没事的
I got you, little brother. You're gonna be just fine.
萨姆  萨姆
Sam, Sam?
小卡
Cass?!
卡西迪奥
Castiel?!
你到底死哪去了
Where the hell are you?
萨姆
Sammy!
不  小卡
No, Cass.
怎么回事
What's happening?
是天使
Angels.
他们坠落了
They're falling.